girlvanic.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy Policy | Girlvanic Studios | Girlvania & Activedolls

## **Privacy Statement for girlvanic.com**

##### **Last updated: 24th May 2018**

This website is operated by Gvanic SL, AD.

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on girlvanic.com. This privacy policy applies to the website and all products and services offered by Gvanic.

Accessing or viewing the contents of this website is expressly and strictly limited to adults 18 years of age and over, and having attained the age of majority in their community. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

### **Information We Collect**

We collect the following information from you:

  * **Information that is automatically collected by our server when you visit our website or use our applications**

Our server will automatically log data regarding each visit such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We may use this information to monitor server errors, server administration or to monitor visitor behaviour. It is not possible for this to be disabled on a per-user basis so you must leave this website and not use our applications if you do not agree to this happening.

  * **Information you explicitly provide to us**

If you contact us by email or by filling a contact form, you may voluntarily choose to provide personally identifiable information (such as your email address), or other potentially sensitive information. Such information will be used only to respond to you and/or to troubleshoot your problem.

If you decide to opt-in to our newsletter, we'll collect your email address for the purpose of sending emails that may include company news, updates, service information, related products, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions in each email.

You are informed and give your consent for the incorporation of this data into the computerised files of Gvanic, registered with the Andorran Data Protection Agency.

Gvanic takes all appropriate steps to limit the risk that all data which may be supplied by you may be lost, damaged or misused.

Gvanic guarantees, in every case, the exercise of the rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition in the terms established by legislation, by sending a communication to the email address contact@girlvanic.com

If legally required to do so, we will disclose to a third party any information we have.

### **Cookies**

This website uses first party cookies which are stored on your browser. This website does not store any information that would allow us to identify individual users of this service. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

Cookie Name | Description  
---|---  
cookiebar | This cookie is used to prevent the appearance of the cookies information banner.  
NoCookie | This cookie is set in order to disable other cookies according to your preferences. This cookie does not store any information.  
_pk_ref.* | 

These cookies allow us to determine whether you are a return visitor to the site, and to track the pages that you visit during your session.

We use them to monitor traffic levels, search queries, referring pages, and visits to this website.  
  
_pk_cvar.*  
_pk_id.*  
_pk_ses.*  
  
**_The cookies are currently ENABLED.  
If you do not want this site to store information on your computer with cookies, click here._**
